>> We've just seen some examples of metrics that are difficult to measure
我们看到了一些指标很难直接测量
directly or even impossible.
或不可能测量
You said, there are some other techniques we can use here, right?
你说过 我们能够使用一些其他技巧 是吗？
>> Right. And these techniques are actually useful
是的 实际上这些技巧对于生成新的指标创意
for generating new ideas for metrics, as well.
也十分有用
And so they're useful for
因此 相比你目前的指标
both the new ideas, as well as digging deeper into a user experience than
它们对于新创意和深度挖掘用户体验
what your existing metrics might be able to get you.
十分有用
>> Great. So what are these techniques?
太棒了 那这些技巧是什么呢？
>> There's a lot of techniques.
有很多技巧
This ranges from surveys to retrospective analyses, to focus groups.
从调查到回顾性分析 到焦点小组
These techniques can be used for both brainstorming new metrics,
这些技巧可用于新指标的头脑风暴
as well as validating possible metrics.
以及验证可用的指标
Now we briefly mentioned several of these techniques back in lesson one,
现在 我们简单回顾下在第一课中提到的几种技巧
but here we're going to be focusing on how to use these techniques to generate
但我们这里将关注如何使用这些技术
ideas for new metrics.
为新指标生成创意
Now we're only going to discuss them very briefly, there are details for
现在 我们只是简单地讨论下
all of what we're going to be talking about in a PDF linked off of
在讲师注释里链接的 PDF 中
the Instructor's Notes.
会有详细的介绍
>> So let's talk first about external data.
首先 我们谈谈外部数据
So when you're looking for external data that's going to help you to define and
寻找外部数据以帮助你定义和验证指标时
validate metrics, the first thing that you can come across is companies that
你遇到的第一件事是
actually collect fairly granular data of that market share vertical such as how
公司实际上采集非常细节的数据 比如市场份额
many people are interested in the travel industry and even for specific websites.
以及有多少人对旅游业 甚至对于某些特定的网站感兴趣
They may have visitor data that the put together.
他们将访客数据合并在一起
So these are companies that just, comScore, Nielsen,
因此 comScore、Nielsen
there's a few others and they all use different techniques.
还有其他一些公司 会使用不同的技术
So the second type of company that'll also have data you might find useful
而会提供你可能认为有用的数据的第二种公司类型是
are those that actually run surveys of user.
对用户进行调查的公司
So these would be companies, such a Pew or Forrester,
如 Pew 或 Forrester
they may ask users how many devices do you have?
它们可能会问用户有多少设备
How much time do you spend on them in a given day?
在一天中花费多少时间使用这些设备
So depending on what you're looking for,
根据你想要寻找的东西
you may be able to either get these types of data from a source your company
你可能会从一个你公司已有的来源得到这些类型的
already has that they may have marketing or for other reasons or
用于营销或其他目的的数据
sometimes you can even get the results published on the web.
有时你甚至能够得到网页上发布的结果
The third category is what I'll call academic research,
第三类 我称为学术研究
although it's a bit broader than that.
但其范围大于学术研究
And these are papers that actually try to establish metrics.
指的是试图建立指标的论文
They may run correlation studies.
它们可能涉及相关性研究
They may have very similar results to, you know,
它们可能具有相似的结果 你知道
how much attention people are paying.
人们有多关注这些论文
So something like eye tracking where you may actually be able to find a study
就像眼动跟踪 你可以看到一项研究
where they had a bunch of people in a lab and they look at how people read
它在实验室内聚集很多人 他们观察人们如何阅读一个网页
a page and they actually collect, you know, how much reading are they doing
他们能够阅读多少内容
versus how much time do their eyes spend on the page
他们的眼睛在网页上能够停留多长时间
versus how long did it take them to actually click-through to the next page.
以及他们点击进入下一页面需要多长时间
So you may be able to find data you need or
因此 你能够发现你需要的数据
you may be able to find something very similar.
或能够发现非常类似的信息
So normally, you can use these in multiple ways as Diane said.
因此 一般情况下 你能够通过 Diane 所说的多种方法使用这些信息
First of all, they're great for brainstorming.
首先 它们非常适用于头脑风暴
They help you think of new metric ideas.
它们能够帮助你想出新的指标创意
The second is they're good for validating metrics, where you can
其次 它们能够验证指标
actually say, you know, on my site, I think I get this many visitors per day.
你可以说 在我的网站上 我每天有这么多访客
But when I look at my whole industry,
但当我纵观整个行业时
it looks completely out of whack with what I'm seeing.
好像跟我看到的完全不一样
So these can help you establish that your own tracking for users or
因此 这些能够帮助你为用户建立自己的跟踪
other sort of aggregate metrics is, is actually working.
或其他总指标 是真的有用
And then the third thing is they can actually help you develop validation
第三 它们能够帮助你开发验证
techniques.
技巧
So, if you see that study about eye tracking you can look at how they
因此 如果你看到关于眼动跟踪的研究 你可以观察
analyze their data and maybe you have other data that you could use and
他们是如何分析其数据的 你可能拥有可以使用的其他数据
you could analyze it in the same way to validate your metrics.
你可以以相同的方式分析它 从而验证你的指标
So they've a lot of different uses.
因此 它们有很多不同的用途